Guide to the Wendell Ricketts papers, circa 1961-2004.
Ricketts, Wendell papers, circa 1961-2004.
- Series IV. Subject Files
  - "Freud on Homosexuality" (article by Wendell Ricketts), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Gays and film (includes programs for 16th and 17th annual SF International Lesbian/Gay Film Festival), 1980-1995 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Gays/lesbians of color, 1987-1992 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Gay/lesbian politics and trends, 1985-1990 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Gay "movement" photographers, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Gay parades, 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Gay rights votes, 1978, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Genet, Jean (includes Playboy v.11, no.4), 1964, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Haring, Keith, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Ginsberg, Allen, 1994, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Grimsley, Jim, 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Groening, Matt (Kids Have Rights Too...), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Hate speech/hate crimes, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Hemphill, Essex, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Hitchens, Donna
    - Campaign lists and pins (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Benefit event materials, May 23, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Campaign news clippings, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - General news clippings, 1990, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Homosexuals Intransigent, "Best of HI" by Craig Schoonmaker, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - House Bill 41 (Hawaii State Legislature), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Howe, Delmas, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Huygen, Christian, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - "In a Different Light" program at the University of California, Berkeley, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Italian news story on Massachusetts gay marriage, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Italian news story on Massachusetts gay marriage--copy, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Italian pamphlet about HIV testing (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Isherwood, Christopher, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Ivins, Molly, 1988, 1991, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Jackson-Paris, Rod, and Bob, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - James White Review: A Gay Men's Literary Journal, Summer-Fall 1987, Spring 1989 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Kantrowitz, Arnie (article on cruising), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Katz, Jonathan (includes article by Ricketts), 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Kellogg, Stuart, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Kepner, Jim, Gay Movement History & Goals and What Do We Have In Common? speeches, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Kiger, Patrick, "The Gay Republican" GQ article, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Koch, Ed, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Leavitt, David, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Lebowitz, Fran, 1979, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Lesbian/gay sororities and fraternities, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Luce, Clare Booth (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - The Male Muse--Young, Ian, ed., 1973 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Man and Society: Journal of the Albany Trust, Spring 1961, Winter 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mandela, Winnie (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Mapplethorpe, Robert (includes "Digital Collections" CD-ROM), 1989-1990, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - March on Washington, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - March on Washington, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Maud's bar/Rikki Streicher, includes Maud's: The First Twenty Years publication, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Maupin, Armistead, 1989, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Merkin, Daphne: A Closet of One's Own, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Merrill, James (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, circa 1981-1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 10-18)
  - Morrissey, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Moss, Howard, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Mr. John, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - National Gay Rights Advocates (NGRA) materials, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Navratilova, Martina, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Near, Holly, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - The New Republic articles on gays in the military and pornography, Feb. 19, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Nickels, Thom- Gays on TV: Life Beyond Sitcoms, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - O Boys--"Manifesto", 1993 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - O'Connor, Sinead, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Offprints, articles, + misc. on gay families and youth, including "Are Bert and Ernie Gay?", 1985-1994 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - O'Hara, Frank, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - O'Keefe, Georgia, 1987, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - "The Origins of Human Sexuality" symposium materials, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Out & Outraged (civil disobedience group), 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - OUT/Write, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - OUT/Write Straitjacket of Rhetoric article by Ricketts, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Outing articles, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Owles, James (obituary), 1993 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Paglia, Camille, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Physique: interviews with body builders, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Picano, Felice interview, by Ricketts, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Pins, including "I Love Castro Street", "Hate Is Not A Family Value", others, and one condom distributed by Gaelforce AID for Irish AIDS, cover states "Loose Mickeys Cost Lives, Saint Paddy Wants You...to wrap it in a 'paddyglove'" (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Plante, David, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Plath, Sylvia, 1989, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - 'Pornographization' article, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - 'Pornographization' related publications, including clothing catalogs such as M2M and Underground, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - 'Pornographization' related clippings, also Christopher and Castro street trading cards, 1994? (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Preston, John, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Prison art, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Prison art (Brown, Frazier--racism), 1998 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Q San Francisco, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Racism/fascism/multicultural debate, 1987-1995 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Racism/fascism/multicultural debate, 1990-1996 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Religious/biblical issues, 1981-1992 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Research: Copies of Professional Papers
    - Charcot et Magnan, Inversion du Sens Genital, 1882 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Fellman & Fellman, The Rule of Moderation in Late Nineteenth-Century American Sexual Ideology, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Ferguson, Ann, The Sex Debate in the Women's Movement: A Socialist-Feminist View (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Freud, Sigmund, various papers, 1904-1910? (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Gurko, Jane and Sally Gerheart, A Lesbian Model of Nonviolent Rhetoric, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Goldberg, Williams, The Birth & Death of the Gay Liberation Movement, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hanckel and Cunningham, Can young gays find happiness in YA books?, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Heller, CG. and Maddock, WO., Clinical Uses of Testosterone in the Male: Homosexuality, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Hirschfeld, Magnus, Ursachen und Wesen des Uranismus, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Ibrahim, Azmy, Deviant Sexual Behavior in Men's Prisons, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Jones, Corky, How to Pick Up Straight Men, 1981? (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Kiernan, J.G., Lecture XXVI, Sexual Perversion, 1884 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Kinsey, Alfred, Criteria for a Hormonal Explanation of the Homosexual, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Lehre, Gregory, Gay Male Fantasies and Realities, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Leznoff and Westley, The Homosexual Community, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Meredith, Nikki, The Gay Dilemma: Why are some homosexual men so promiscuous?, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Miller, Brian, Gay Fathers & Their Children, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Money, J. and Bohmer, C., Prison Sexology: Two Personal Accounts of Masturbation, Homosexuality, and Rape, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Persichetti, N., In Memoriam: Caroli Henriki Ulrichs, 1896 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Raffalovich, M.A., Uranism, Congenital Sexual Inversion, 1895 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Richmond, Katy, Fear of Homosexuality & Modes of Rationalization in Male Prisons, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Rosenzweig, S. and Hoskins, R.G., A Note on the Ineffectualness of Sex-hormone Medication in a Case of Pronounced Homosexuality, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Roth, Loren, Territoriality & Homosexuality in a Male Prison Population, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Saliba, Pat, Research Project on Sexual Orientation, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Tully, Carol and Albro, Joyce, Homosexuality: A Social Worker's Imbroglio, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Ulrichs, K.H., Inclusa and Araxes, (translated by Michael Lombardi) (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Ulrichs, K.H., Manor: Eine Novelle, (translated by Lombardi), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Ulrichs, K.H., Vier Briefe, 1862 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Ulrichs, K.H., Vindex and Memnon, 1898 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Van Gelder, Lindsy, Marriage as a Restricted Club, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Walker, Alice, When Women Confront Porn at Home, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Weinberg, Martin, Gay Baths and the Social Organization of Impersonal Sex, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Wittman, Carol, Refugees from America- A Gay Manifesto, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Romer v. Evans, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Richards, Ann, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Richards, Renee, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Riggs, Marlon, 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Rosenkrantz, Robert, circa 1992-2000 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Rosenkrantz, Robert: Alone with the Devil, Ch. 4, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Ross, M., info on The Treatment of Homosexuals with Mental Health Disorders, includes article by Ricketts, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Rouilard, Richard, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Rudnick, Paul, Jeffrey, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Saint, Assoto, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - San Francisco Bay Guardian, Pride '92 issue, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - San Francisco Board of Education on hate crimes against LGBT students, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - San Francisco Examiner: Gay In America Special Report, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 35-37)
  - Sarton, May, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Schulman, Sarah, 1988, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Sex and Relationships Course/AASECT presentation, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Sex, Love, Mores, Dating, 1984-1995 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Sex Surrogates/IPSA, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Sexuality Today: The Professionals' Newsletter, December 1980 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Simmons, Joe, article by Ricketts, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Simon, William & Gagnon, John, Homosexuality: The Formulation of a Sociological Perspective, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Sischy, Ingrid (Artforum), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Sadism/Masochism
    - Bound & Gagged reader survey, Issue 48 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - CUIR Underground newsletter, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - "Dangerous Top" notice (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - DSM Project/Race Bannon, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - GL-ASB listserve: Nazi's and uniform fetish, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - GL-ASB listserve: Top/bottom ratio, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Lexicon (leather publication), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous s/m related information, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Piercing/cutting and AIDS, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Play spaces/sex clubs, 1992? (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - QSM publication, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - "Rasberry Pie" articlue for the SandMutopia Guardian, by Ricketts, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Response to Dorchen Leidholdt's "Lesbian S/M: Sexual Radicalism or Reaction" (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - The Ring publication, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Sadism and Masochism, circa 1988-1994 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Toys for sale (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - TRUST (fisting publication), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Various publication, including issue #28 of Bound & Gagged, 1981, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - "Smart Perverts" flyer (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Sontag, Susan, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Spender, Stephen, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Stonewall 25- New York City, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Streicher, Rikki (Maud's--a lesbian bar) (article by Wendell Ricketts), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Sullivan, Andrew, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Tennant, Stephen, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Thompson, Karen and Kowalski, Sharon, 1988, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Thompson, Mark (gay spirit), 1987 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Transsexualism, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - University of Hawaii Files
    - The Paper, MCC, Honolulu, HI, circa 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - UH Gay Alliance materials, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - A Strategy for the Measurement of Homophobia, by Walter Hudson and Wendell Ricketts, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Methods of Assessing Sexual Orientation project, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - How Much Homosexuality on the Head of a Pin?, paper by Ricketts, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Styles of Intimacy in Men's Relationships, by Ricketts and T. Fresquez, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Class questions on homosexuality, 1981-1982? (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Sex surrogates research, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Biology & Homosexuality: Ansell's Cow or Occam's Razor?, by Ricketts, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Vanity Fair magazines with gay related articles, May, Aug. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Vidal, Gore, 1987, 1990, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Vreeland, Diana, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Wagstaff, Sam, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Warner, Doug, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Warner, Doug: photographs (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - "What Time and Newsweek Didn't Tell You", re: March on Washington 1987, article by Ricketts (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - White, Dan (San Francisco Examiner special), 1985 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Wolfe, George C., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Woods resort case article by Ricketts, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - The Word Is Out, University of California, Irvine publication, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Youth and sexual orientation, 1998, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Rejection from Medical Aspects of Human Sexuality, 5/19/1982 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - "Homosexuality in Adolescence: The Reification of Sexual Personalities", by Ricketts, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - "Biological Research on Homosexuality: Ansell's Cow or Occam's Razor?", by Ricketts, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Cruse comic copies/corespondence, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - For Better or for Worse comic strip reprints/permission for use, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Gay men relationship survey, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Bright, Susie, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Fried Green Tomatoes movie reviews, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Ireland, Patricia, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Italian AIDS brochure (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Kovick, Kris, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Television, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Azpadu, Dodici: "Carve Hearts" (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - D'Arezzo, Daniel story, "Symposium" (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Gilgun, John writing to review (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Mecca, Tommi Avicolli story "Fireflies", 2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Professional correspondence, 1980-1995 (Box 12, Folder 23-24)
  - Writings by others (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Homosexuality in adolescence: The reification of sexual personalities (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Adolescents-literature review summaries (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - NAMBLA (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Drummer magazine lawsuit
    - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Press releases (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Legal research (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Notes and miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Desmodus (layoff), 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Out-of-pockets (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Desmodus, Inc. work correspondence, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Legal papers, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Hongisto, Richard - newspaper clippings (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Purple Circuit newsletter (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Assembly Bill 1, Discrimination in Public Accommodations, Employment (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Lady Green: Greenery (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Gay press list (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - GLAD-Boston, MA (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Gays and military/ROTC (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Gay marriage/domestic partners (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - American Psychiatric Association-newsletter of the Gay Caucus (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Lesbian/Gay Law Notes, Bar Association for Human Rights of Greater New York (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - GLAAD executive director candidates (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - National Lesbian/Gay Law Association newsletters (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Equity Institute; Hampshire College, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Democratic Convention, San Francisco, 1984; (newspaper clippings) (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Gays, 1980s; (newspaper clippings) (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Love questionnaire (Greenwell and Hatfield) (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous book information (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - O'Hara, Scott (correspondence) (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Matlovich Society-Portland, Maine (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Interview questionnaires and schedules (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Gay and Lesbian Almanac Project - Lynn Witt (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Clinical measurement package - Walter Hudson (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - "For Love, Life & Liberation: First Person Accounts of the Lesbian and Gay Nonviolent Civil Disobedience at the U.S. Supreme Court", October 13, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Adolescent sexuality (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Seven Deadly Sins, [movie poster and mini-DVD] (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Italian pamphlets, brochures and other ephemera (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous publications and flyers (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Continental Baths towel (Box 13)
  - Research articles by others, A-N (Box 14)
    [arranged in alphabetical order]
  - Research articles by others, O-Z (letter size), A-Z (legal size) (Box 15)
  - Surveys on men's relationships, 1 folder (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous oversize newspaper clippings and publications (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Stonewall 20 poster, June 1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Series V. Erotic Photographs
  - Attomar Studio (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Baron, Todd (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Bond, David (Darrell Sickel), July 26, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Brocke, Todd (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Bruce Steel and Lou Thomas? (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Converse, John (Dak), Behind the Barn, June 25, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Converse, John and George Csabon (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Converse, John and Walsh, Dennis, Fire Island, July 2, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Coxe, Kevin (Box 9, Folder 9-13)
  - Crane, Brad (Al Tremain) (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Della University, Tony ("Angelo" in Javelin #1) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Gordon, Michel (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Kelly, Joe (Bill Sawyer) (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - King, Jon (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Knight, Ryder (Zeus) (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Kramer, Tim (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Likens, Eric (The Eagle) (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Lopez, Joe and Dino (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Martin, Scott (photographer) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - McDonald, Chris (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - McGloshor, Ron (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - "M.H. and Friend" (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Negron, George, NYC, Jan. 18, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - NYC, Jan 28, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 28-29)
  - O'Hara, Scott (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - O'Hara, Scott (photographer) (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Preston, John (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Rage, Christopher (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Sardi, Dom (Box 9, Folder 34-37)
  - Sardi, Dom slides (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Scala, Greg, LA, Jan. 1978 (Box 9, Folder 39-40)
  - Sherrod, David (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Solos, Fire Island, July 31, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 42-43)
  - Stampel, John (Metecue Association) (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Target Studios miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Tom of Finland (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Unidentified (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Venetucci, Ed (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Walsh, Dennis (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Wander, Burt (Metecue Association) (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Zechel, Ron (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Unidentified (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Series VI. Audiovisual Materials
  - Audiotapes
    - Tom Bustameile, Jack Lapier and David McEwan, et. al., 1988 (Box 10)
      Series III. AIDS Resource Files - Hawaii
    - Dave McEwan, 6/27/88 (Box 10)
    - Life Foundation (Box 10)
    - Clarysse Kami, SLUSHS, Denny Pomeroy-steamworks, and Steve DeMaggio (begin); Denny-steamworks- cont'd and Steve DeMaggio (finish) (Box 10)
    - Buzz Bense, 12/6/89 (Box 10)
    - Scott O'Hara, 4/6/88 (Box 10)
    - Celia Farber, 10/3/92; (3 tapes) (Box 10)
    - Bob Guccione, 10/17/92 (Box 10)
    - Felice Picano, 7/10/86 (Box 10)
    - Mark Thompson- Gay Spirit, 8/15/87 (Box 10)
    - Jonathan Katz/Jack Collins; Summaries Interrogs. and J. Katz rebuttal, 1/6/92; 8/3/87 and 1/10/92 (Box 10)
    - Rikki Streicher, 7/14/89 (Box 10)
    - Philip Core, 1/4/89 (Box 10)
    - Mark Milano, 10/15/93 (Box 10)
      Series III. AIDS Resource Files - Long-term survivors
    - Aldyn McKean, 10/7/93 (Box 10)
    - Charles Caulfield and Ken Wythe-Dickinson, 10/10/93 and 10/11/93 (Box 10)
    - G. Steven Rose- LTS/Out Story, 10/6/93 (Box 10)
    - Cindy Patton/Michael Callen (Box 10)
    - Michael Callen, 10/9/93 (Box 10)
    - Martin Delaney, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Barry Freehill and Dr. Abdul Alim Muhammad, 7/6/92 and 7/7/92 (Box 10)
    - Drew Hopkins, Rob Costello and Peter Staley, undated and 10/20/92 (Box 10)
    - Fauci, 5/20/92 (Box 10)
    - Jane Po/Jeff Bender; Jane Po/Jeff Bender- PI and Joe Sonnabend, 11/10/92; 11/16/92 (Box 10)
    - Darby Davenport, 6/18/88 (Box 10)
    - JoAnn Loulan and Donna Hitchens, 2/90 (Box 10)
    - Nancy Polikoff, 9/30/90 (Box 10)
    - Nan Hunter, 1/18/89 (Box 10)
    - Roberta Achtenberg- LRP, 1/17/88 and 1/6/89 (Box 10)
    - Steven Fritz-Rudzer and Michael Hodges, 7/30/88 and 7/31/88 (Box 10)
    - Judy Early, 9/12/89 (Box 10)
    - Rikki Westerchulte, 12/10/89 (Box 10)
    - Donna Hitchens, 7/14/88 (Box 10)
    - "Forum on Gay Men and Lesbians as Foster Parents", A. Freebury, 2/27/92 (Box 10)
    - Dr. Peter Duesberg, 7/22/92 (Box 10)
    - WNSR 105FM- "Kids: The Thing of the Future" (Box 10)
    - National March on Washington Media (Box 10)
    - 60 Minutes- "Acceptable Risks", 10/4/92 (Box 10)
    - OUT/Write '91 Keynotes (Box 10)
    - OUT91- "How Can We Politicize the Censorship Debate?" (Box 10)
    - Music for Life-volumes 1 and 2, November 6, 1987; 2 cassette audiotapes (Box 11)
  - Videotapes
    - Gay Cuba (Box 10)
    - Demand A Cure Forum (West Hollywood Park Auditorium, West Hollywood, CA), September 29, 1994; VHS videotape (Box 11)
  - Photographs
    - Slides from various marches/demonstrations (Box 12, Folder 25)
      Includes: Lucca-Le Mura San Frediano (?); ACT-UP Demo- post ASTRA/Foscarnet action, 6/92; AIDS Cure ACT-UP Demo, San Francisco, 5/22/94; Names Project, Washington DC, 10/11/87
    - Photographs by various photographers, mainly relating to theater, art and entertainment (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Italian gay event, April 1994; [oversize photograph] (Box 13, Folder 4)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
The following materials have been separated and cataloged individually:
20 Questions About Homosexuality: A Political Primer. New York: Gay Activists Alliance, 1972?.
A & U: America's AIDS Magazine. No. 78.
Advocate Men. v.1:no.1,8 (1984: June, 1985:May)
Altman, Dennis. Homosexual Oppression and Liberation. New York: Dutton, 1971.
Antoniou, Laura (ed). Looking for Mr. Preston. New York: Masquerade Books, Inc., 1995.
Approaching 2000: meeting the challenges to San Francisco's families: the Mayor's Task Force on Family Policy. (1990) By San Francisco (Calif.). Mayor's Task Force on Family Policy.
Arenas, Reinaldo. Before Night Falls. Dolores M. Koch, tr. New York: Penguin Books, 1993.
Arts & Letters: Journal of Contemporary Culture. Issue 6, Fall 2001.
Babilonia. No.173.
Bad Attitude. Vol. 1, issues 1-4 (1984/1985); vol. 2, issues 1-3 (1985/1986); vol. 3, issues 1-2 (1987).